lexicata.com 2016-03-16

# Lexicata | Law Firm CRM & Client Intake Software

### **Lexicata Privacy Policy**

LawKick Inc. (doing business as Lexicata) collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Website. This Privacy Policy lays out what information we collect and how we use it. By using our service, you are also agreeing to be bound by our Terms and Conditions.

**Information Collection & Use**

_Registration and Sign Up_

In order to use this Website, you must first complete the registration form and create an account by inputting your name, email address, a subdomain, and a password. We collect your personally identifiable information during this registration step, and during the sign up process that follows. After registering, you are asked to provide your law firm contact information (such as law firm name, address, phone number, and a logo). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. We also request your credit card information to charge you for the Lexicata service plan that you’re signed up for.

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, and promotions. If you wish to opt out from these emails, you can do so from your account settings.

_Subscription_

Lexicata is a subscription based service. As a registered member we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form to process your subscription. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, physical address, company name and address) and financial information (such as credit card number and expiration date).

We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

_Account Information_

We collect some third party personally identifiable information on our site. When a user creates an account, they have the option to add contacts and/or clients to their account. The clients’ information is never viewed, sold, released, or otherwise disclosed or utilized by Lexicata. Our software uses this information solely to facilitate communications between users of Lexicata and their clients (such as sending out forms, signature requests, or other email communications). We do not share this information with any third parties for advertising or promotional purposes.

_Uses of Information_

Lexicata may, from time to time, use the personally identifiable information collected from our users for the purposes of understanding our users’ geographic and demographic distribution, to improve and modify our products to better meet our users’ needs, and to enable effective communication with our customers.

**Communications from the Site**

_Special Offers and Updates_

We will occasionally send you information on products, services, and promotions, as well as updates from the company. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. You can opt out at any time from your account settings.

_Blog Updates and Newsletter_

We send you weekly updates from our blog with information about running a law firm, technology and the law, practice tips, and more. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications. You can opt out at any time from your account settings or by clicking the “unsubscribe” link at the bottom of any email.

_Service-related Announcements_

We will send you service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, or we make significant changes to the functionality or design of the website, we might send you an email update.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, as they are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

_Customer Service_

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to help you manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, live chat, or telephone, depending on which is more appropriate for the given circumstances.

_Log Files_

As is true of most Websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our userbase as a whole.

We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information. We use a third-party tracking service (Google Analytics) that uses cookies [log files] to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate.

_Cookies_

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and/or persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. For more information on cookies see http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie.

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.

_Profile_

We store information that we collect through cookies, and log files to create a “profile” of your preferences. We do not tie your personally identifiable information, to information in the profile. We use this information in order to provide you a tailored user experience while on our site. [Such as remembering your password so you don’t need to log-in each time.] We do not share your profile with any third parties.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

_Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)_

We may share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our partners and advertisers. This information does not identify individual users.

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

_Agents_

We use an outside credit card processing company (Stripe or Paypal) to bill you for subscription services. We do not retain, share, store or use your personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

We also use outside, third party, services to handle certain transactions such as scheduling and sending emails or collecting signatures. You may be required to register for certain services in order to use them. Please note that you must adhere to their terms and conditions and privacy policy, so please read those carefully before deciding to use these features of our site.

_Legal Disclaimer_

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, subpoena, or legal process served on our Website or company.

_Choice/Opt-out_

We provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in each newsletter or communication, from your account settings,  or by emailing us at support@lexicata.com.

You will be notified when your personal information is collected by any third party that is not our agent/service provider, so you can make an informed choice as to whether or not to share your information with that party.

_Links to Other Sites_

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Lexicata. Please be aware that we, Lexicata, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Website that collects personally identifiable information.

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Website.

_Blogs and Other Forums_

If you use the blog on this site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there in post comments or elsewhere can be read, collected, or used by other blog visitors, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit publicly on our blog or other forums.

_Access to Personally Identifiable Information_

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on your account settings page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@lexicata.com.

_Security_

The security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use every commercially acceptable means possible to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. However, when you enter sensitive information (such as your credit card number) during the payment process we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL) to ensure maximal security and safety.

If you have any questions about security on our Website, you can send email us at support@lexicata.com

_Business Transitions_

In the event Lexicata goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

_Changes in this Privacy Statement_

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us:

**By email:**

support@lexicata.com

**By mail:**

LawKick, Inc.

2520 Overland Ave.

Los Angeles, California 90064
